vokle.com 2011-12-31

# Vokle

## Privacy Policy

**This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 4, 2009.**

Vokle is founded on the principles of helping people engage in dialogue with the world's most innovative thinkers, doers, movers, and shakers. We're users of the web just like you, and understand that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the vokle website and/or using the service, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

The Straight Talk
     We wrote this policy out to tell you a little more about what we do to protect your personal information at Vokle. We will change this policy at any time if necessary (most likely if there is an inappropriate action by a fellow member). we'll post it up clearly on the front page if there need to be changes, but by continuing to use the site, you agree to abide by the revised privacy policy. 
The Legal Talk
     Vokle provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at www.vokle.com ("Site" ) or collected through our live discussion platform, including via SMS, WAP and Instant Messaging ("Service" ). Vokle may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Vokle website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 
     By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the U.S. your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the US. 
     If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at privacy at vokle dot com 

### 1\. Information Collection and Use

The Straight Talk
     In order to use participate in the events, you have to sign up. Your user name will be visible in the events you attend. We'll use your email to contact you in case we need to get a hold of you or notify you of any upcoming events that we feel may interest you. Speaking of events which interest you, like most sites, we use cookies to see how the site is used and where we can improve it. We'll do our best to only contact you with events and speakers which we feel may interest you. You can always unsubscribe from emails. (I know I wouldn't want anyone's inbox to look like mine after I signed up for meetup). 
The Legal Talk
     Our primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the product and services made available through the Site, including, but not limited, to the Service, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one. 

Information Collected Upon Registration.
     If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to Vokle. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service, or if you desire to receive marketing materials and information. 
Additional Information
     Your full user name is displayed to people in the Vokle network to enable you to connect in a more personal way. If you contact us by email, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you. 
Use of Contact Information
     In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. 
Log Data
     When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data" ). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service 

### 2\. Cookies

The Straight Talk
     Enabling cookies allows us to remember your settings and are only used for purposes to better understand how you interact with the site, so we can make the cool parts cooler, and rework or drop the unpopular parts. If you want to block cookies you can do that on your browser, but keep in mind that then flash will always want to reconfirm your camera settings upon entry. 
The Legal Talk
     Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. Vokle may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

### 3\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

The Straight Talk
     We do use some third party services such as servers for video streams and database storage. We will only disclose information necessary in order to complete specific tasks. In the event that Vokle gets bought out, (don't bet on it), or goes under, we'll give you some options of what we do with the information if it differs substantially from this privacy document. 
The Legal Talk

Service Providers
     We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, database storage and management. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data. 
Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement
     Vokle cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Vokle or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law. 
Business Transfers
     Vokle may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

### 4\. Changing or Deleting Information

The Straight Talk
     Contact us at privacy at vokle dot com if you are registered and want to update or correct any information. 
The Legal Talk
     If you are a registered user of the Site, you may access and update or correct the information you provided to us by e-mailing us at privacy at vokle dot com 

### 5\. Security

The Straight Talk
     We care about privacy of information and will do our best to keep it private. If anything arises regarding a breach of that information we will notify as soon as we have taken measure to correct the issue, and after we have cooperated with the needs of law of enforcement if necessary. 
The Legal Talk
     Vokle is interested in safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. 
     We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

### 6\. Links to Other Websites

The Straight Talk
     We do not endorse any links to third party sites which are posted by users within the events. Please use caution before clicking on a link, and be aware that some of those sites may place their own cookies on your computer. 
The Legal Talk
     Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

### 7\. Our Policy Towards Minors

The Straight Talk
     This site is intended for adults 18yrs of age and older. We do not purposefully collect any information for those who create accounts and are underage. If you find your child has an account please contact us at privacy at vokle dot com. We will delete any accounts we discover that belong to those under 18yrs of age. 
The Legal Talk
     The Site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at privacy at vokle dot com. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If we become aware that someone under 18 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

### 8\. Conditions of Use

The Straight Talk
     By visiting and using Vokle's website and/or service, your visit and any dispute is subject to this privacy policy and our terms of use. 
The Legal Talk
     If you decide to visit Vokle's website and/or use the service, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.
